A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Administrative Manuals and Post reports FA720
Rockefeller Archive Center
- North Africa (Tunisia) - Manual of Administrative Procedures and Policies for Expatriate Personnel, 1973 January 1 (Box 1 (SK42034), Folder 22)
- West Africa (Ghana) - Administrative Services and Regulations for Expatriate Staff, 1970 June 1 (Box 1 (SK42034), Folder 23)
- West Africa (Nigeria) - Nigeria Post Report, 1962 March (Box 1 (SK42034), Folder 24)
- West Africa (Nigeria) - Administrative Services and Regulations for professional staff, 1965 June (Box 1 (SK42034), Folder 25)
- West Africa (Nigeria) - Manual for Office Administration and General Services, 1970 January (Box 1 (SK42034), Folder 26)
- West Africa (Nigeria) - Administrative Manual for Expatriate Personnel in Nigeria, 1970, 1971 January (Box 1 (SK42034), Folder 27)
- West Africa (Nigeria) - A General Guide to Lagos for newly arriving Ford Foundation personnel, 1971 July (Box 1 (SK42034), Folder 28)
- Burma - Post Report and Information Kit, 1957 May - 1958 (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 1)
- India - Organization and Management Guide, 1963 December (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 2)
- India - India Post Report, 1965 (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 3)
- India - "Welcome to Calcutta" and "Getting to Know Delhi" distributed by American Women's Club, 1964, 1967 (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 4)
- India and Nepal - Organization and Responsibilities of the Ford Foundation India Field Office, 1966 February (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 5)
- India - Administrative Policy Procedure for Ford Foundation Professional Staff in India, 1966 April (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 6)
- India - Bhubaneswar Post Report and Bhopal Post Report, 1968 May, 1966 December (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 7)
- India - Medical Portfolio, 1967 February (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 8)
- India - Handbook for Indian Administrative Services Staff, 1968 March (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 9)
- India - Post Report, 1970 May (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 10)
- India - Ford Foundation Building, 1968 (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 11)
- Indonesia - Post Report, 1971 February (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 12)
- Indonesia - Personnel Policies and Practices for Indonesian Staff, 1970 May, 1972 April (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 13)
- Pakistan - Post Reports, 1954 October, 1961 June (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 14)
- Thailand and Southeast Asia - Personnel list and report, 1967 (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 15)
- Argentina and Chile - Briefing Information and Administrative Guides, 1963, 1964, 1965 (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 16)
- Chile - Briefing Information for Assignment in Chile, 1971 (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 17)
- Colombia and Venezuela - Coming to Colombia, 1965 January, 1968 January (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 18)
- Colombia and Venezuela - Staff Policy Guide, 1976, 1980 (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 19)
- Mexico - Administrative Manual, 1964 August (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 20)
- Mexico - General Information, 1965 (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 21)
- Mexico - Staff Handbooks, 1967, 1971, 1972, 1979 (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 22)
- Peru - Administrative Guide, 1978 (Box 2 (SK42035), Folder 23)